EMAD UDDIN

Full-Stack Developer and UI Designer

https://emad-uddin.com

+8801303653528 emad.uddin.0001@gmail.com

With over 5+ years of development & design experience. Developing enterprise and client base software and web solutions and related to User Interface & User Experience of business requirements with a strong sense of ideation, conceptual development and design thinking across different media.

EXPERIENCE

Technical Associate

Oct 2021 - Now

DigiPro Solution Ltd

Development various kinds of web and mobile app for own organization and clients.

Web and Software Developer

Oct 2021 - Oct 2022

MonsterClaw LLC

Development and design SaaS tools for own organization and clients.

Mobile App Developer

Mar 2022 - Now

AgileX (Weekend Part Time)

Develop a SaaS base ultimate HR Solution.

Web and Mobile app Developer

Sep 2019 - Oct 2022

A'qa Technology

Developing new features and user interface from wireframe models.

Developed modern web application with Node js, JavaScript, ES6, VueJs, NuxJs, SQL and No-SQL.

Extensive knowledge about mobile app development with Flutter and Dart.

Working with firebase console (ML, Realtime database and Notification etc.) and also working with Google Vision API

IT Expert

Apr 2017 - Sep 2019

Development Design and Consultant Ltd.

Working in Bogra Pally Bidyut Samity-2 as an IT Solution Expert and AutoCad Over head electricity distribution system Designer.

SKILLS

JavaScript, ES6, Vue JS and Nuxt JS, Node JS, PHP & Laravel, Dart & Flutter, MySql, Firebase, Mongo DB, Shopify Liquid, UI & UX Designer.

SOFTWARE

VS Code, Android Studio, Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma and much more.

LANGUAGE

English, Bangla

EDUCATION

CSE

Presidency University

Dhaka.

HSC (Science)

Kabi Nazrul Govt. College.

Dhaka.

SSC (Science)

Jubilee Institute

Bogra.

PERSONAL INFO

Nationality Bangladeshi

Current Place Dhaka